他相信道理简单明了
One would believe in simple means
有人觉得也非不可能
Some would believe it possible
其他人则是漠不关心
Others feel it won't be seen
但没人相信会有奇迹
For none believe in miracles
有人用钻石换碎石
Some give a diamond for a stone
有人用碎石换钻石
Some give a stone for a diamond
有人守著自己的钱财
Some keep all things for their own
而也有人什么都不说
And some remain in silence
纯朴的古代，有位小女孩
There once lived a girl in a simpler time
皮毛与头发如昼夜般
with night-like hair and skin so white
不论她到哪，都对大家说
Wherever she went, everyone she'd tell
「似是己所有，尔可当己用」
"What'd appear as mine, 'tis thine as well"
她旅行四方，捐出她所有
So she went through the world, giving all she had
从来没想过要拿回来
never feeling the need to claim it back
不论她到哪，大家都臣服
Everyone she'd meet would befall her spell
「虽是己所有，尔可当己用」
"What appears as mine, 'tis thine as well"
虽然她已时日不多
Counting the days of a shortening life
却仍坚持大方作风
Living the ways of a nursery rhyme
哼声有如钟声一般
Humming the tune of a ringing bell
虽是己所有，尔可当己用
What appears as mine, 'tis thine as well
他相信道理简单明了
One would believe in simple means
有人觉得也非不可能
Some would believe it possible
其他人则是漠不关心
Others feel it won't be seen
但没人相信会有奇迹
For none believe in miracles
有人用钻石换碎石
Some give a diamond for a stone
有人用碎石换钻石
Some give a stone for a diamond
有人守著自己的钱财
Some keep all things for their own
而也有人什么都不说
And some remain in silence